<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Patrick Moehrke</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Patrick Moehrke</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Education &amp; Certifications</title><link>/education/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/education/</guid><description>Education Link to heading Stellenbosch University | BCom Honours Actuarial Science Link to heading 2020
Honours Research Project
Evaluating the use of genetics to calculate risk premiums with applications to Huntington’s Disease
This project was very interesting for three main reasons:
The topic exposed me to genetics and how one can construct survival models for genetic diseases All of the modelling needed to be performed from first-principles (as there were no available packages) which made me more comfortable with scientific computing and numerical methods It was my first real exposure to LaTeX and taught me how R can interface with LaTeX to produce pretty tables and plots.</description></item><item><title>Experience</title><link>/experience/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/experience/</guid><description>Dupro Advisory | Actuarial Consultant Link to heading 2020-Present
Responsibilities Link to heading In this role I perform a mix of internal business development and client-facing work, including but not limited to:
Developing and delivering data science and cloud training activities related to actuarial and insurance use cases. Providing technical consultancy services related to statutory and regulatory industry requirements. Providing technical and operational consultancy services related to data, machine learning, and cloud computing within a financial services context.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>I am an actuarial consultant with strong experience in machine learning, mortality analysis, IFRS 17, and presenting training workshops &amp;amp; talks.
My background is in actuarial science. I have obtained 9 exemptions and I am registered as a TASSA.
I have been lucky enough to be on projects covering a wide breadth of tech, from web dev to Linux administration to cloud computing. This has helped me quickly pick up new frameworks and libraries depending on the project, and develop a solution that is tested, well-documented, and easily communicated back to clients.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon</title><link>/posts/placeholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/placeholder/</guid><description>Blog posts are coming soon!</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>I would love to connect! Reach out to me through GitHub or LinkedIn. Alternatively, send me a message below:
Send a message Visitor Count:</description></item><item><title>Interests</title><link>/interests/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/interests/</guid><description>I enjoys reading Stephen King novels and 60s science fiction, researching lost &amp;amp; unknown music over at r/lostwave, training gymnastics, and going for wine and beer tasting around Stellenbosch, South Africa.</description></item></channel></rss>