<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Homepage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>I am an actuarial consultant with strong experience in machine learning, mortality analysis, IFRS 17, and presenting training workshops &amp;amp; talks.
My background is in actuarial science. I have obtained 9 exemptions and I am registered as a TASSA.
I have been lucky enough to be on projects covering a wide breadth of tech, from web dev to Linux administration to cloud computing. This has helped me quickly pick up new frameworks and libraries depending on the project, and develop a solution that is tested, well-documented, and easily communicated back to clients.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon</title><link>/posts/placeholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/placeholder/</guid><description>Blog posts are coming soon!</description></item><item><title>Experience</title><link>/experience/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/experience/</guid><description>Below is an overview of my work experience to date:
Actuarial Consultant @ Dupro Advisory Link to heading 2020-Present | Stellenbosch, Western Cape, ZA Link to heading Responsibilities Link to heading In this role I perform a mix of internal business development and client-facing work, including but not limited to:
Developing and delivering data science and cloud training activities related to actuarial and insurance use cases. Providing technical consultancy services related to statutory and regulatory industry requirements.</description></item><item><title>Interests</title><link>/interests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 18:35:58 +0200</pubDate><guid>/interests/</guid><description>Patrick enjoys reading Stephen King novels and 60s science fiction, researching lost &amp;amp; unknown music over at r/lostwave, training gymnastics, and going for wine and beer tasting around Stellenbosch, South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>I would love to connect! Reach out to me through GitHub or LinkedIn. Alternatively, send me a message below:
Send a message Visitor Count:</description></item></channel></rss>